MAKAZIWE BLESSING MAGAGULA

Ferndale, Randburg 2194 | 072 981 8469/ 068 070 7826 | Code 8 Driver's License | makaziwem23@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Energetic Junior Software Developer and graduate in Information Technology with experience in software development. Willing apply knowledge, skills and experience to effectively fill a position within the IT sector. I am a hardworking and dedicated intern who can be reliable upon to help your company achieve its goals. Currently enrolling in Honours Degree in Computing

WORK EXPERIENCE

MAY 2021 - PRESENT JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, ALEXANDER FORBES

- O Produce clean, efficient code based on specifications in C#, JavaScript, MVC, .NET Framework
- Contributing in the SDLC and implementation of Agile Methodology
- Integrate software components and debugging existing source code
- O Conducting peer reviews, testing and problem solving in writing code and other methods
- API development and integration

FEB 2020 – APR 2021 | SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN, ALEXANDER FORBES

- Produce clean, efficient code based on specifications in C#, JavaScript, MVC, .NET Framework
- Troubleshoot, debug and upgrade existing software
- Integrate software components and third-party programs
- Executing database queries using SQL Server
- API development and integration

FEB 2019 – JUN 2020 | SYSTEMS DESIGN & ANALYSIS STUDENT ASSISTANT, NORTH-WEST UNIVERSITY

2018 – 2019 | PUBLIC RELATIONS OFFICER [VOLUNTARY], BACKSLASH INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SOCIETY (NWU)

EDUCATION

2021 - PRESENT

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE HONOURS IN COMPUTING | UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH AFRICA (UNISA)

- Natural Language Processing
- Software Engineering
- Software Project management
- Research Methods and Proposal

2017 - 2019

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY | NORTH-WEST UNIVERSITY

- Databases
- Systems Design & Analysis
- Java
- Operating Systems
- Networks

2016

NATIONAL SENIOR CERTIFICATE | LIGBRON ACADEMY OF TECHNOLOGY

- Mathematics
- Physical Sciences
- Business Studies
- Computer Applications Technology (CAT)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- C#
- Java
- ASP.NET
- .NET Framework
- MVC
- Databases (MySQL, SQL)
- JavaScript
- Azure DevOps
- Microsoft Office

REFERENCES

Name MRS. IMELDA SMITH

Occupation/Relation Lecturer

Contact 078 740 8488

Name MR. NTAKADZENI THARAGE

Occupation/Relation Direct Manager

Contact 082 262 5862

Name MR. KARL BEISSNER

Occupation/Relation Manager

Contact 072 513 9520